Guide to the Harry L. and Mary K. Dalton Collection, 1695-1955 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- T-Z
  - Woodruff, Isabella papers, 1768-1865
    This collection contains correspondence, primarily containing observations of a social and political nature regarding the period in South Carolina before, during and immediately following the Civil War. Much of the subject matter deals with viewpoints of the women. Correspondants include: her mother, Mrs. Louisa Roberts; her brother, Samuel C. Roberts; and her best friend, Countess Aniela N. Pinkind, as well as Charles F. A. Holst, her future husband.